ngojobsinafrica.com 2019-04-09

# Privacy Policy – NGO Jobs

Ngojobsinafrica.com is Africa’s largest Job site that focuses only on Non-Government Organization job Opportunities across Africa.  We publish latest jobs and career information for Africans who intends to build a career in this industry (NGO). Please read our Privacy Policy below if you intend to use our service.

 ** _What information do we collect_**  
we collect information such as Name & Email, Address you when you register on our site. This information is necessary to keep you updated on latest Ngo Jobs in your country. You may however visit the site anonymously.

 ** _What do we use your information for?_**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one following ways:  
– To personalize your experience  
– To send you periodic updates on our services.  
– To administer a survey or contest on our site.  
– To improve our customer service (respond to your request easily and faster).

 ** _How do we protect your information?_**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

 ** _Do we use cookies?_**  
Yes we use cookies to maintain your session on our site and to service you relevant third party ads

 ** _Do we disclose any information to our outside parties?_**  
We do not sell trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  
However during the cause of search by employers, information such as your resume, job objective, resume, name and pic will be revealed to employers to enable them choose the best candidate and to contact you.  
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non -personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising and other uses.

 ** _Third Party Links_**  
Please refer to our disclaimer section at www.ngojobsinafrica.com/disclaimer/

 ** _Online Privacy Policy Only_** This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 ** _Terms and Conditions_**  
Please refer to our terms and conditions  
**_Your Consent_**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy

 ** _Changes to our policy_**  
If we decide to change our policy we will post those changes on this page.

 ** _Unsubsription_**  
If at any time you wish to stop receiving our Information/updates/alerts you can unsubscribe by clicking on the Un-subscription link in our newsletters or send a request to Hello@ngojobsinafrica.com.

 **Disclaimer**

Ngojobsinafrica.com is Africa’s largest Job site that focuses only on Non-Government Organization job Opportunities across Africa.  We publish latest jobs and career information for Africans who intends to build a career in this industry (NGO). Please read our Privacy Policy below if you intend to use our service.

 ** _Job Scams_**  
**Ngojobsinafrica.com publishes** latest jobs and career information for Africans who intends to build a career in this NGO industry. This site offers exclusive NGO Job Opportunities In Africa. We do not in any way expect visitors/candidates or job seekers to pay any form of money to apply for jobs or as a criteria be shortlisted for interviews.  
Please do not pay to any organization that claims to be Ngojobsinafrica.com. We neither solicit nor request for money from job seekers to provide job, expect in cases where a user subscribes for our premium services.  
Employers or agencies that ask for money, are fake, they might be scammers and fraudsters: none of these forms of requests originate from either our site or that of any of our affiliates.

These sort of scams may be a part of the notorious Advance Fee Fraud, popularly known as 419. Please beware!!!
